You, the Doctor, Tony Tony Chopper!
Boil me or cook me alive!
Give me your worst, you bastards!
Now, an unlikely duo must win the second round,
the Groggy Ring, to get Chopper back.
Disappointed? Not at all.
Round two, shoot it into the Groggy Ring!
Chirp, chirp!
Our mighty Groggy Ring combatants have taken the field!
Opposing them on the Straw Hats team,
their meddlesome sideline supporter from the first round,
the Savage Chef, Sanjay!
I think you mean Stylish Chef.
And beside him, with a bounty of 60 million berries,
Pirate Hunter, Ro-Ro-Noah Zorro!
Hardly worth our time to squash a couple of pipsqueaks like these.
Right, Big Pan?
He can't hear you.
Man, what do these guys eat?
Well, start this out with a coin toss.
Tails.
What about you?
Uh, kinda has to be heads, right?
Tails!
Field or ball?
Ball, please.
You heard him!
Our Groggy Monsters have chosen them all!
The Straw Hats Ball Man will now enter the other team's mid-circle.
Left or right?
Doesn't matter.
In case you were wondering,
the Ball Men are the players with the silly little hats on their heads!
Knock your opponent's Ball Man into the ring on their side of the field,
and the game is yours!
Just get on with it!
Hey, Ball Man, get in position already.
Now listen, I never agreed to be the Ball in the first place.
You better shut your mouth unless you want to boot to the teeth.
How am I supposed to look cool with this thing on my head?
You gonna cry over a hat?
Hey, that looks good on you!
You think I'm gonna fall for that stupid?!
Zoro!
Sanji!
I'm counting on you!
I'm sorry we lost the last round, you guys!
It's up to you now!
Please get Chopper back!
You gotta!
Wow, would you look at that?
It's a real Wotan!
They aren't as large as pure-blooded giants, but he's still pretty big.
Don't bother cheering for your friends!
It's no use!
Those guys are more than just muscle!
They're groggy ring experts!
Oh, hey, split-head!
Did you want something?
He said it again!
Poor boss!
Why would you be so cruel to this sweet, gentle man?!
What's with that face?
If you're afraid I'm going to interfere again, then don't worry!
I won't even need to in this round, you babies!
Don't tell me you can butt in on this game, too!
Yep!
It all depends on how the captain feels!
Naturally, some pilots like to fight fair and square so they can test the strength of their crew!
Others will cheat any way they can to make sure they never lose a match!
But I just do whatever I want!
Fe-fe-fe-fe-fe-fe-fe-fe!
I don't see why you're complaining about a little foul play here and there!
If you're a real pirate, you should be used to these sorts of things!
Right?
The sea is treacherous!
Oh, yeah!
You would know!
Three!
By the way, your team looks to be playing a game of their own!
They do know the match is about to start, right?
Three!
Laugh while you still can!
They're just laid back because they know they can win!
I saw that, cheater!
You went too early on that last one!
Shut up!
You're just mad because you lost!
Like you always do!
What?
I always lose, huh?
We'll just see about that!
Let's do best three out of five!
And just lose again?
So is the chef your ball man or what?
Hurry up!
Is that what those idiots are arguing about?
Sanji!
That hat looks great on you!
All right!
Let's rock!
Ball man's here to kick some ass!
Gotta admit it does suit you.
You look like a real prince!
From the kingdom of lame asses?
Wasting time!
Start the match!
You suck!
No, you suck!
Hey, hold it!
No weapons on the face!
You suck!
No, you suck!
No weapons on the face!
You suck!
No!
No weapons on the field, pal. You gotta lose the swords.
Huh? Those the rules?
Yeah, because this is a ball game.
Can't have you slicing each other up, now can we?
Fine. My fists are all I need.
You sure you're going to be okay out there?
A swordsman without his swords is just, well...
What?
A normal guy, only lamer.
That wasn't even a good bird!
Get over it!
It certainly took long enough, but it looks like the Straw Hats ball man is finally making his way to the opponent's circle.
Hey, Cook, hope you get trampled out there.
Of yours.
The crowd is hungry for action today!
Big Pan, are you ready to make some grown men cry?
Huh?
P-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p.
He can't hear you.
Come on, man!
Pay attention for once!
It's not that funny! Stop laughing!
What can I say? The groggy monsters are always up for a good laugh!
Now!
Now, why don't we go over a few quick rules?
There's no time limit, and the first team to score wins!
So all we gotta do to win this is knock Jumbo's head into the ring on their side.
Simple enough.
The hard part's gonna be stopping them from planting the cook's head in our ring.
Can Team Straw Hat win back the reindeer they lost in round one, or will they lose another member?
As you can see, Foxy's returning champs are laughing in the face of their competition.
But will they be the ones to laugh last?
The whistle is about to sound!
Let the game begin!
We start with Ball Man Sanji, deep in enemy territory.
Will he retreat or attack?
Let's do this!
Tackle Machine Pickles takes off with a heavy charge!
Okay, just gotta head for their Ball Man and finish him off.
Sling Tackle!
Get out of my way!
Let's see what you got, Big Man!
I hope that fat hat of yours fits in the goal!
It's gonna be a Ball Man fight!
Oh, yeah!
Hey, what's going on here?
Skin's all slimy!
The chef is slipping and sliding on Big Pan's massive arm!
But that's no surprise!
After all, Big Pan's a loach-fished wootan!
They have slippery skin!
What the heck are you doing?
Stop screwing around!
Running gun!
Get down here!
You better watch what you wish for, sword man!
Long pass!
This is it!
Big Pan Super Long Pass!
Sling!
Team Captain Hamburg races onto the scene for the catch!
But Zoro is in hot pursuit as well!
If that stupid head of yours makes it anywhere near the goal, I'm gonna chop it off!
You talk big!
But just wait till I get down there!
Now my sweeping tackle!
Pickles crosses over the rival team's line!
Meanwhile, Hamburg flies high for a fancy mid-air catch!
Perfect!
And then...
I got it!
Pickles dashes into position!
Get back here, dammit!
Toro goes for an interception!
Spending tackle!
Uh-oh!
With his partner down, Ballman Satchi isn't spiraling into the sky!
Satchi!
Bringing up the rear, Big Pan storms across the field and catches the falling ram bird!
Pongrously!
Once again, Hamburg nabs Satchi with a perfect catch!
Incredible!
The ring is inside!
Is this it?
You can't go down that easy!
Yeah!
Oh!
There you go!
Yeah!
It's the Hamburger Dove!
Come about!
Hurry!
Do something!
Toro!
Satchi!
The straw hats are running out of time!
I know.
I'm honest.
You don't need to remind me.
It ain't over!
I won't let you score!
All right, you've had your fun.
Time to put me down, fathead.
I can't let Zoro bail me out of this.
I'd never hear the end of Earth.
And stay down.
No goal!
Balmintachi is back on the ground
and looks like he's ready for some more action.
I can take care of myself just fine.
Got it?
If you could stay on the ground, ball.
It seems our groggy monsters
have finally found some worthy adversaries in the ring.
This one will be a match to remember.
Chirp, chirp!
The Strawheads prevail, but can they do it again?
We've seen pigs fly once today, so anything can happen.
The Challengers seem to be discussing their next move.
Let's get ready for round two.
You're cramping my style.
Go back to the sidelines, Mosshead.
Is it your style to get pounded like a punching bag?
Whoa, dude.
They're tough.
That guy picked up pickles and tossed them.
I've never seen Hamper go flying like that.
Stay out of the way and I'll win this.
I can't stay out of the way.
I'm the bald man.
The only one that matters.
No!
Hamper, what are you doing out there?
If you lose, I'll never ever forgive you!
Listen, you good for nothing.
Playboy cook!
You better get those fancy eyebrows out of my way in a hurry.
No, you listen, you dumb oaf!
If you don't get your meathead off the field right now, I'm gonna fry it up!
What's this?
The Straw Hat team seems to be having some sort of disagreement with each other.
Both bald men are still in play, so let's hope they can channel some of that aggression in a more productive direction.
Those two sure are funny, aren't they?
You idiots!
Now's your chance!
What are you doing?
They're bald men all alone!
Gang up on him and knock him in the ring while those other guys are still out of the game!
Big Pan stops him for a surprise attack on the Straw Hats!
Whoa!
Too bad guys!
Don't run for the ball!
How are you supposed to score?
Hey, I'm doing my best here, but that guy's got knives on his shoes!
If we don't run away, he's gonna make mulch out of us!
Hey, Ruff!
I thought you said we could use weapons!
What?!
He's not even trying, is he?!
Hey, hey, hey!
You can't expect him to catch every little thing, can you?
He's got a bad name!
Stop screwing around!
Oh!
Sanji, what were you thinking?
You saw the whole thing!
I saw you sweating over there, you little cheater!
No!
No way!
I...
I didn't see nothing!
Not a thing!
You liar!
Hey!
That's the rift, Sanji!
You're gonna get in trouble!
Yellow card to Sanji!
A Team Straw Hat!
You want another boot to the face?!
Whoa!
Hold on!
You're only gonna make it worse!
And there it is!
A yellow card for Sanji!
Just one more of those, and the chef will be ejected from the game once and for all, folks!
Shut up!
I'll eject you!
And the threats keep coming in from the foul mouth ball man!
Who knows who he'll lash out at next?!
Why don't you come down here and say that to my face?!
What is he, a gangster?
Worry about the boots, the ref can wait.
Wait, an axe?
You can't miss that!
I didn't see.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure!
Look!
He's got a giant axe you can see for yourself, stupid!
Give it up!
You're gonna get a red card if you don't shut it!
Why are you siding with them all of a sudden?
We're gonna get Julienned out there!
I know, but they're trying to make you do something stupid!
You're playing right into their trap!
Who cares?
If you won't do it for me, at least do it for Chopper!
Okay!
Stand back and let me handle them!
No!
We don't need the captain butting in and complicating things!
Sanji, please!
Win the match for me!
I won't let you down!
That was easy.
Alright, now back to the game!
If you're gonna do that again, why even bother?!
Running around like this is getting us nowhere!
Yeah, but now that we know their game plan, we can come up with a counter attack!
Get ready, big man!
It's payback time!
Go back to the sidelines!
This bastard is mine!
There's plenty of it for the both of you!
Answer!
All three are about to collide!
If I attack him where his skin's exposed, I'll just end up slipping around like last time!
That leaves his hands, his feet, his mask, and his underwear!
Don't spoil his eye!
Up!
You're tracing circles!
Oh!
Uh-oh!
Here comes Big Pan's signature move!
Things are about to get slippery!
Bring it on!
Who's afraid of a little skating, right?
Now there's no escape!
No escape!
I'm gonna lose my life!
Come on!
Don't look together, guys!
Really!
It looks like Pickles and Habberg have finally recovered from their earlier accident!
Yeah!
They're back in it!
Slaughter them, guys!
And what's this?
It seems that they've updated their wardrobe!
Their leader Habberg is sporting some iron knuckles and elbow guards!
Where did those come from?
Meanwhile, Pickles has donned Spike's shoulder protectors!
Those clearly violate the no-weapons rule!
But by complete coincidence, the referee seems to be doing some stretches right now!
Oh well, you can't expect him to catch up or anything, right?
Four!
What?
Time for revenge, my friend!
You ready?
Here goes...
Lord's Coastal!
Whoa!
Stop betting!
Now we'll bring the pain!
Let's do...
Spinning Tackle!
The clammy monsters launched a counterattack, but this time their target isn't the Ballman,
but his partner Zoro!
This is about to get ugly!
Hamburger Heaven!
Zoro!
But the assault isn't over yet!
It pan-readies yet another brutal attack!
Hamburg is brandishing his mighty elbow guards and preparing for an attack!
And preparing for an heir to ground strike!
Oh no!
This is bad!
The Straw Hats are about to learn the power of teamwork!
Like an arrow, raining from the sky!
Huh?
Sue?
Bea-spark Atch!
No!
A direct hit?!
A direct hit?
He won't be walking that one off.
By the way, fatalities are a common occurrence in the groggy ring,
in case you didn't know.
So dizzy.
And now the Fugsy team turks their attention to the Straw Hacked Ballman!
Human!
Come on!
Pickles and his spikes are closing in fast!
Sanji!
Move!
Straight Tackle!
What? You thought that was it?
They're just getting started!
Guns attack?
Pepper sends him flying back!
They don't even care about scoring anymore!
The Graggy Monster stopped the competition
flat with the spectacular three-man team attack!
It's such a cruel way to win!
Get up, Zoro!
Come on, Sanji!
Both balls are still in play, but it looks like Team Straw Hat is down for the count!
It's a cake!
No!
In fact, you might say they're...
Now all that's left is to stuff the Ballman in his coffin!
I mean, gold!
And it'll be two wins in a row for the Foxy Pyre!
It just goes to show you can't keep a good monster down!
Looks like we win again!
The Graggy Monster is still in play, but it looks like Team Straw Hat is down for the
count!
It's a cake!
No!
In fact, you might say they're...
The Graggy!
Now all that's left is to stuff the Ballman in his coffin!
I mean, gold!
And it'll be two wins in a row for the Foxy Pirates!
It just goes to show you can't keep a good monster down!
Looks like we win again!
Hey, let's work together for ten seconds.
Okay, fine.
But no longer.
The Graggy Monster is still in a row for the Foxy Pirates!
On the next, One Piece, a barrage of red cards and groggy ring.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!